Guide to the Charles Henry Pace and Frankie M. Pace Gospel Music Collection CAM.PAC.1999.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Charles Henry Pace and Frankie W. Pace Gospel Music Collection
1927–1958
1943-1947
ULS Archives & Special Collections
CAM.PAC.1999.01
14.48 Linear Feet (183 Printer Plates, 6 Boxes)
The Charles Henry Pace and Frankie M. Pace Gospel Music Collection includes printer's plates, negative proofs, and printed music. The collection provides a valuable research tool for the Paces' career, demonstrating how the Old Ship of Zion Music Company and Charles H. Pace Music Publishers conducted business. While the date range of the collection comprises 1927–1958, the bulk of the material dates from 1943–1947.
History
Charles Henry Pace (b. 1886, Atlanta Ga.; d. 1963, Pittsburgh, Pa.) and Frankie Mae Pace (née Scott; b. 1905, Clinton, La.; d. 1989, Pittsburgh, Pa.) were influential gospel musicians and Civil Rights activists, first in Chicago, Illinois, and then in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania.
Charles was born in Atlanta, Georgia, and his family moved north when he was young, eventually settling in Chicago in 1899. He studied trumpet and piano as a child, and his professional career began in 1910, when he conducted a dance band in Benton Harbor, Michigan, and started a publishing company, Pace Music House, in Chicago. Prior to the 1950s, most of his publications were arrangements of songs by other songwriters, including Charles Albert Tindley, Thomas Dorsey, and Roberta Martin.
Around 1915 he began working as an arranger for Chicago-based Lillian M. Bowles, an early publisher of African American sacred music. He became choir director at Beth Eden Baptist Church in the Morgan Park neighborhood of Chicago in the mid-1920s. Drawing from the membership of the church choir, he assembled the Pace Jubilee Singers, which ranged from seven to ten musicians and was briefly accompanied by Thomas Dorsey. The group performed on WGN, WLS, and WBCN and recorded eighty-five sides for Victor, Brunswick, and other labels. As some of the first recordings made of this repertory, they were very influential.
Around 1934 he stopped working for Bowles and began working at Liberty Baptist Church. Also around this time he married Frankie, and together they established the Old Ship of Zion publishing company. In 1936 Reverend A. W. Nix invited Charles to serve as music director at Tabernacle Baptist Church in the North Side neighborhood of Pittsburgh. After arriving in Pittsburgh, the Paces quickly started the Pace Choral Union, a gospel choir of twenty-five singers that was enlarged to as many as 300 singers for special performances.
The Paces moved Old Ship of Zion to Pittsburgh, establishing a store and office on Centre Avenue in the Hill District. The store was an important community meeting place and hub for visiting musicians, including Louis Armstrong and W. C. Handy. Since gospel was not supported by major publishing companies, the Paces published their own music and distributed it through a network of agents, becoming some of the nation's most successful gospel publishers. In 1952 they started a new company, Charles H. Pace Music Publishers, through which they published most of Charles's own compositions. Charles grew ill in 1959, and Frankie assumed full business responsibilities. When Charles died in 1963, she changed the name to Pace's Music Store.
The store and the Paces' musical careers became integral components of their community work and activism. Frankie was especially politically active, taking a leadership role in many organizations. She was president of the Hill District Homeowners and Tenants Association, president of Citizens for Hill District Renewal, and a board member on the Mayor's Committee on Human Resources, Urban League for Pittsburgh, Opportunities Industrialization Center, Allegheny Housing Rehabilitation Corporation, and NAACP of Pittsburgh.
Scope and Content Notes
The materials of the Charles Henry Pace and Frankie M. Pace Gospel Music Collection date to between 1927 and 1958, with the bulk from between 1943 and 1947. Care was taken to retain the original order of the collection, which is divided into four series and arranged by type: printer's plates, negative proofs, printed music, and miscellaneous.
A substantial portion of the collection involves printer's plates. Consisting of 254 plates, this series provides extensive insight into the Old Ship of Zion Music Company and Charles H. Pace Music Publishers' operations. The majority of plates consist of pages of music, with some lithographs also included.
The collection also includes many negative proofs used for publishing sheet music by the Old Ship of Zion Music Company and Charles H. Pace Music Publishers. This series includes, but is not limited to, songs, title bars, graphics, and business forms. Particular strengths of this series are the complete negatives for songs such as "Hold Not Thy Peace," "I Must Tell Jesus All," and "Lead Me All The Way."
The third series consists of printed music, subdivided into music by Pace and other songwriters' music. Pace's songs are arranged alphabetically, with the other subseries also organized alphabetically according to songwriter. Records of particular note are the 208 copies of Pace's "Roll Memories Roll" and numerous works by Thomas A. Dorsey and Kenneth Morris, such as "Wings Over Jordan" and "Till We Meet Again," respectively. The main weakness of this series is the multiple incomplete copies of "Jericho." Moreover, the copyright dates of many songs are unknown.
The miscellaneous series includes a postcard addressed to Charles Pace, dated April 28, 1957, requesting the publication of "Divine Love." There are no personal or business papers included, however the collection provides a valuable research tool for the Paces' music work, demonstrating how the Old Ship of Zion Music Company and Charles H. Pace Music Publishers conducted business.
Acquisition Information
Acquired from the American Social History and Social Movements Auction, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, August 1999. Accession # 1999/1
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Bibliography
The bibliography contains a dissertation, sheet music, sound recordings by the Pace Jubilee Singers, and dealers of records and sheet music used in developing the finding aid.
Charter, Samuel, Gates, J.M., Johnson, Bunk, et.al. An Introduction to gospel song. 3d. ed. New York, N.Y.: 2001. Features: "Leave it there," with Hattie Parker.
Martin and Morris Music Company Records, 1930-1985, #492. Series 3: Sheet Music, circa 1930-1985 – Subseries 3C: Other Publishers: Box 7 #21 – "Chas. H. Pace." Smithsonian, National Museum of American History, Archives Center.
Montgomery, Elvin – Culture Resource. ph: 212-666-4449 / fax: 212-666-8212.• #43 Sheet Music: Pace Jubilee Singers. Features: "43 Most Popular Negro Spirituals with Guitar Chords. Circa 1933. Arranged by Chas. Pace Cole. Publishing Company, Chicago. 64pp. Pictoral cover with photograph of the 7-member group set against a silhouette of a tree in the background. VG $50."
Nevins, Richard. How can I keep from singing – early American religious music and song. Vol. 2. 2d. ed. Newton, N.J.: Yazoo, 1996. Features: "Oh death."
New Orleans University Olee Club, Pace Jubilee Singers, Pilgrim Jubilee Singers, et.al. Black Vocal Groups – complete record works with four bonus tracks. Vol. 7, 1927-1941. Vienna, Austria: Document Records, 1997. Features: "I'll be satisfied," "It pays to serve Jesus," He's the one," and "You'd better mind."
Pace Jubilee Singers. Amazing Gospel. Hoboken, New Jersey: Music Club, 2001. Features: "Certainly Lord."
Pace Jubilee Singers. The half ain't never been told – early American rural religious music: classic recordings from the 1920s and 30s. Vol 1. 2d ed. U.S.: Yazoo, 1999. Features: "Certainly Lord."
Pace Jubilee Singers. O Brother: the story continues. Portugal?: Music Club, 2002.Features: "O Death."
Pace Jubilee Singers, C.&M.A. Gospel Singers/ Quintet, and Four Harmony Kings.Pace Jubilee Singers and C.&M.A. Colored Gospel Quintet (date unknown). Vol. 2. 2d. ed., 1928-1929. Vienna, Austria: Document Records, 1998. Features: "What a Friend," " Nothing betw.," "Ezekiel saw de wheel," "Stand by me," "Leave it there," "Old-time religion," "When the saints go marching in," "Seek and ye shall find," "My Lord's going to move this wicked race," "Every time I feel spirit," and "I'm going to do all."
Pace Jubilee Singers and Four Harmony Kings. Pace Jubilee Singers and Four Harmony Kings, 1921-1924. Vol. 1. 2d ed., 1926-1927. Vienna, Austria: Document Records, 1998. Features: "You gonna reap just what," "Everybody get to walk," "My Lord, what a morning," "My Lord is writin' all the time," "I'm going thru Jesus," "I do, don't you," "Is it well with your soul today?," "Were you there when they crucified my Lord," "Heaven's door's gonna be closed," "Lawdy, won't you come here," "My Lord will deliver," "Walk in the light of God," "His eye is on the sparrow," "I've started and I'm goin' all the way," "Don't you want to meet your mother over there," "We will walk through the valley of peace," "Shouting on," "Oh death!," and "Certainly Lord."
Pace Jubilee Singers with Hatiie Parker. In my heart. Richmond, I.N.: Gennett, 1928.
Tyler, Mary Ann L. The Music of Charles Henry Pace and Its Relationship to the Afro-American Church Experience. Ph.D. Diss. University of Pittsburgh, 1980.
"Bread of Heaven," 1945. Martin and Morris Gospel Sheet Music Collection. Chicago Public Library. #50817.
"Don't You Want To Shout Hallelujah Over There," 1942. Martin and Morris Gospel Sheet Music Collection. Chicago Public Library. #508217.
"He Keeps the Fire Burning," 1947. Martin and Morris Gospel Sheet Music Collection. Chicago Public Library. #508392.
"He'll Say 'Well Done' Some Day," 1947. Martin and Morris Gospel Sheet Music Collection. Chicago Public Library. #508433.
"Hide My Soul," 1943. Martin and Morris Gospel Sheet Music Collection. Chicago Public Library. #508479.
"I'll Spend My Vacation in Heaven," 1934. Martin and Morris Gospel Sheet Music Collection. Chicago Public Library. #508675.
"I'm Not Ashamed," Date Unknown. Martin and Morris Gospel Sheet Music Collection. Chicago Public Library. #508708.
"In That New Jerusalem," 1945. Martin and Morris Gospel Sheet Music Collection. Chicago Public Library. #508735.
"Joy, Joy, Joy (I Shouted)," 1946. Martin and Morris Gospel Sheet Music Collection. Chicago Public Library. #508840.
"My Road Is Rough and Rocky All the Way," 192? Martin and Morris Gospel Sheet Music Collection. Chicago Public Library. #509001.
"It's you nobody but you," 1913. Howard B. Waltz Music Library. University of Colorado.
"Out of the Depths of My Soul," 1945. Martin and Morris Gospel Sheet Music Collection. Chicago Public Library. #509076.
Roots and Rhythm. ph: 888-ROOTS-66 / fax: 510-526-9001.• The Pace Jubilee Singers/ Four Harmony Kings, Document 5617. Vol. 1.1921-1924. $14.98.• The Pace Jubilee Singers/ C.&.M.A. Colored Quartet, Document 5618. Vol. 2, 1928-1929. $14.98.
"The Rose That Made Me Happy Is The Rose That Made Me Sad," 1913. Roses In Popular Song, part 1. Parlor Songs.
World of Gramophones. ph: 719-528-7122.• Going Thru Jesus/ Lord What/ Morn. Pace Jubilee Singers. #154- B129 "78 10" "Single." KIC 20225. E- $6.50.• My Lord What Morning/ Thru Jesus. Pace Jubilee Singers. #145- T201 "78 10" "Single." VIC SCR: 20255. V- $2.50.
"Table is Set so Come and Dine, The" 1935. Martin and Morris Gospel Sheet Music Collection. Chicago Public Library. #509082.
Sheet music; Printing plates; Proofs (Printed matter); Music; Sacred songs -- Scores; Gospel music -- Scores; Choruses, Sacred -- Scores; African Americans -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Women -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Old Ship of Zion Music Company; Pace, Charles Henry; Charles H. Pace Music Publishers; Windom, A. B. (Aaron Bash); Thames, Mary; Morrow, Lillian; Morris, Kenneth; Jackson, Emma L.; Graham, Anne, vocalist; Martin, Roberta, vocalist; Dorsey, Thomas Andrew; Pace, Charles Henry -- Songs and music; Pace Jubilee Singers -- Tabernacle Baptist Church (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
- Printer's Plates, 1939-1958; 1943-1947; I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  This series contains 254 printer's plates used by the Old Ship of Zion Music Company and Charles Henry Pace Music Publishers for printing sheet music. It also includes printing tools such as a hammer, a wire, and nails. The plates are arranged alphabetically beginning with songs and lithographs. The printing tools follow with the numerous unidentified plates concluding the series.
  - "A-men," Page 2, 1.
  - "As I Journey On," Page 2, 2.
  - "As The Years Roll By", 3.
  - "Because of You" Page 6, 4.
  - "Can I Ride" Pages 2, 3, 6, 5.
  - "Can I Ride By" Page 4, 6.
  - "Can You Say, 'Thy Will Be Done?'" Title Page, Page 2, 2, 7.
  - "Climbing Up To Glory Shouting Hallelujah" Page 2, 8.
  - "Come To Return No More" Unidentified Page, 9.
  - "Deeper for Jesus" Page 2, 10.
  - "Don't Let The Day Pass Away Before The Sun Goes Down" Title Bar, 11.
  - "Don't You Want to Shout Hallelujah Over There" Pages 2, Unidentified, 12.
  - "The End of the Road" Unidentified Page, 13.
  - "Everybody Will Be Happy" Page 2, 14.
  - "Fling Out" Page 2, 15.
  - "Give Me My Flowers While It's Yet Called Day" Pages 2, 4, 5, 16.
  - "Go, Go Tell It Every Where" Title Page and Unidentified Page, 17.
  - "Gone To Return No More" Page 2, 18.
  - "Great Jehovah" Page 2, 19.
  - "Greet the Morning With A Hallelujah Song" Pages 2, Unidentified, 20.
  - "Hallelujah, He's the King" Pages 2, 4, Unidentified, Unidentified, 21.
  - "He is Real" Pages 2, 3, 22.
  - "He is Sweeter As the Years Roll By" Page 2, 23.
  - "He Keeps the Fire Burning Down in My Soul" Pages 2, 2, 3, 24.
  - "He Said If I Be Lifted Up" Page 2, 25.
  - "He Will Wipe Away All Tears" Page 2,2, Unknown; 26
  - "Heav'n" Page 2, 27.
  - "He'll Meet Me at the End of the Road" Page 2, 2, 28.
  - "He'll Say "Well Done" Some Day" Pages 2, 3, 29.
  - "He'll Say Well Done, The Last Mile of the Way," Page 2 and First Bar, 30.
  - "He's All and All To Me," Page 2, 31.
  - "He's Alpha and Omega To Me," Page 2, 32.
  - "He's Everything To Me and He's Alright," Page 2, 33.
  - "Hold Me in The Hollow of Thy Hand," Page 2, 34.
  - "Chorus Chant of 'I am Nothing'", 35.
  - "I Am Satisfied," Page 2, 36.
  - "I Can't Forget," Page 4, 37.
  - "I Just Go On," Page 2, 38.
  - "I Know He Will Take Care of Me," Page 2, 39.
  - "I Must Tell Jesus All," Page 2, 40.
  - "I Shouted Joy, Joy, Joy Because He Set Me Free," Title Page, Pages 2, 2, 3-5, 41.
  - "I Tarried All Night Long, Until the Holy Ghost Fell On Me," Page 2, 42.
  - "I'll Anchor By and By," Page 2, 43.
  - "I'll Give Up My Cross For My Crown," Page 2, 44.
  - "I'll Make It In," Page 2, 45.
  - "I'm Born Again," Page 2, 46.
  - "I'm Depending On You, Lord," Title Bar, Page 2,2, 47.
  - "I'm Going To Cling To The Cross Till I Die," Page 2, 48.
  - "I'm Going To Hold To The Cross Till I Die," Page 2,2, 49.
  - "I'm Going To Walk and Talk With My Jesus Some Day," Pages 2,2,3, 50.
  - "I'm Going Up the Rough Side of the Mountain," Page 2, 51.
  - "I'm Going With Him All The Way," Page 2, 52.
  - "I'm Gonna Feast and Never Get Hungry," Pages 2, Unidentified, 53.
  - "I'm Not Ashamed To Say I Love Him," Pages 2-5, 54.
  - "I'm On My Journey," Pages 2, Unidentified, Unidentified, 55.
  - "I'm Saved," Page 2, 56.
  - "I'm Walking With Jesus By My Side," Pages 2,2,3, 57.
  - "In That Morning," Page 2, 58.
  - "In That New Jerusalem," Page 2,2, 59.
  - "It's All Over Me," Page 2, 60.
  - "I've Started and I'm Going All The Way," Page 2, 61.
  - "Jericho," Pages 2-4, 7, 62.
  - "Keep Me Humble Lord," Title Bar, 63.
  - "Lead Me Jesus, All The Way," Page 2, 64.
  - "Let Me Feel The Same Kind of Power Over Here," Title Bar, Page 2,2, 65.
  - "Look For Me For I'll Be There," Page 2, 66.
  - "Love, Love Divine," Page 2, 67.
  - "Meet Me Where There'll Be No More Good-By," Pages 2, Unidentified, 68.
  - "The Morning," Page 5, 69.
  - "My Road is Rough and Rocky All The Way," Page 2, 70.
  - "My Son," Pages 2,4, 71.
  - "Nobody But You Lord, Nobody But You," Page 2, 72.
  - "Not A Word," Pages 2-4,6,7, 73.
  - "No. 34," Unidentified Page, 74.
  - "O Lord, Have Mercy," Page 2, 75.
  - "Oh What A Night," Page 2, 76.
  - "Oh, Yes, He's Mine," Page 2,2, 77.
  - "Oh Yes He Will," Pages 2-4, 78.
  - "Opening Service", 79.
  - "Out of the Depth of My Soul," Unidentified Page, 80.
  - "Pace's Gospel Choral Union, 'Ten Long Years Ago'", 81.
  - "Pace's Spiritual Medley No. 101", 82.
  - "Pace's Spiritual Medley No. 102", 83.
  - "Ride on, Jesus," Page 2, 84.
  - "Rise, Shine, Give God the Glory," Page 2, 85.
  - "Rocking In My Jesus Arms," Title Bar and Page 2, 86.
  - "Roll Memories Roll," Title Page, Pages 2,4, 87.
  - "Sacred Blood," Pages 2 and Unidentified, 88.
  - "Sing, Sing, Ethiopia, Sing," Page 2, 89.
  - "Smile When Things Go Wrong," Page 2, 90.
  - "Some Thing That's New," Pages 2, Unidentified, Unidentified, 91.
  - "The Star," Page 2, 92.
  - "Sweeping Through the Pearly Gates," Title Bar, 93.
  - " The Table is Set So Come and Dine," Page 2, 94.
  - "There'll Be Joy Up There," Page 2, 95.
  - "There's A Bright Light Shining In My Soul," Title Bar and Page 2, 96.
  - "There's A Change In Me," First Bar and Page 2, 97.
  - "Time is Winding Up," Page 2, 98.
  - "Trump of God Will Sound," Page 4, 99.
  - "Trying To Make Heaven My Home," Pages 2-5, 100.
  - "Walk With Me Lord. Walk With Me," Page 2, 101.
  - "Was That You?" Pages 2,2,3,4, 102.
  - "We Will Shout Hallelujah After While," Page 2, 103.
  - "When Every Thing Goes Wrong, Steal Away and Pray," Page 2, 104.
  - "When I Behold My Savior's Face," Page 2, 105.
  - "When I Get Home," Page 2, 106.
  - "Who So Ever Will," Page 2, 107.
  - "You Gonna Reap Just What You Sow," Pages 2-5, 108.
  - "You'll Find Him There," Unidentified Page, 109.
  - Invoice, 110.
  - Invoice, 111.
  - Old Ship of Zion Logo, 112.
  - Image of African-American Woman with Accordian, 113.
  - Image of Bride and Groom, 114.
  - Image of a Family, 115.
  - Jesus image, 116.
  - Pace Image, 117.
  - Rose Graphic, 118.
  - Rose Graphic, 119.
  - Image of Two Women and Man, Possibly Pace, 120.
  - Hammer, 121.
  - Nail, 122.
  - Fastened group of nails, 123.
  - Wire, 124.
  - Wood block, 125.
  - Wood Block, 126.
  - Unidentified Title Bar, 127.
  - Unidentified Page 4, 128.
  - Unidentified Page 4, 129.
  - Unidentified Page 4, 130.
  - Unidentified Page 5, 131.
  - Unidentified Page 5, 132.
  - Unidentified Page 6, 133.
  - Unidentified, 134.
  - Unidentified, 135.
  - Unidentified, 136.
  - Unidentified, 137.
  - Unidentified, 138.
  - Unidentified, 139.
  - Unidentified, 140.
  - Unidentified, 141.
  - Unidentified, 142.
  - Unidentified, 143.
  - Unidentified, 144.
  - Unidentified, 145.
  - Unidentified, 146.
  - Unidentified, 147.
  - Unidentified, 148.
  - Unidentified, 149.
  - Unidentified, 150.
  - Unidentified, 151.
  - Unidentified, 152.
  - Unidentified, 153.
  - Unidentified, 154.
  - Unidentified, 155.
  - Unidentified, 156.
  - Unidentified, 157.
  - Unidentified, 158.
  - Unidentified, 159.
  - Unidentified, 160.
  - Unidentified, 161.
  - Unidentified, 162.
  - Unidentified, 163.
  - Unidentified, 164.
  - Unidentified, 165.
  - Unidentified, 166.
  - Unidentified, 167.
  - Unidentified, 168.
  - Unidentified, 169.
  - Unidentified, 170.
  - Unidentified, 171.
  - Unidentified, 172.
  - Unidentified, 173.
  - Unidentified, 174.
  - Unidentified, 175.
  - Unidentified, 176.
  - Unidentified, 177.
  - Unidentified, 178.
  - Unidentified, 179.
  - Unidentified, 180.
  - Unidentified, 181.
  - Unidentified, 182.
  - Unidentified, 183.
- Negative Proofs, 1927-1958; II.
  The folders are arranged by topic, beginning with songs, continuing with graphics and business forms, and ending with page-proofs.
  - "Can I Ride," Title Bar, 1.
  - "Don't Let the Day Pass Away Before the Sun Goes Down," Title Bar, 2.
  - "Dreaming of You," Unidentified Page, 3.
  - "Go, Go Tell It Ev'ry Where," Title Page and Last Page, 4.
  - "Gone To Return No More," with First Page of I Tried the Lord, 1948; 5.
  - "Hallelujah Hallelu," Page 2, 1950; 6.
  - "Hallelujah He's The King," Title Page and Last Page, 7.
  - "He is Real," Title Page and Page 4, 8.
  - "He Said If I Be Lifted Up," Page 2, 1935; 9.
  - "He'll Say "Well Done" Some Day," Title Bars and Page 2, 1947; 10.
  - "Hold Not Thy Peace", 1958; 11.
  - "I Must Tell Jesus All", 1947; 12.
  - "I'm Walking With Jesus By My Side", 1940; 13.
  - "In That New Jerusalem," Title Bar, 14.
  - "I'se Just A Wond'rin," Last Page, 15.
  - "I've Started and I'm Going All the Way", 1927; 16.
  - "Jericho," Unidentified Page, 1945; 17.
  - "Keep Me Humble Lord," Title Bar, 18.
  - "Lead Me All The Way", 1958; 19.
  - "Let Me Feel The Same King of Power Over Here," Incomplete Page 2, 20.
  - "Merry Christmas, Happy New Year," Title Page, 1940; 21.
  - "Nobody But You Lord, Nobody But You", 22.
  - "Chorus of Some Day I'll Understand", 23.
  - "Waking of Spring," Title Page and Page 2, 24.
  - "When You've Done Your Best," Title Page and Last Page, 25.
  - "Who So Ever Will", 26.
  - "Without A Song In Your Soul," Unidentified Page, 27.
  - "You Can Tell Him All Your Troubles", 1936; 28.
  - You'll Find Him There, Last Page, 29.
  - Various Pages and Bars of Unidentified Songs, 30.
  - Images for "Artist Copy", 31.
  - "Charles H. Pace, Music Publisher," Title Bars, 32.
  - Picture of Choir and Picture of Ladies with Phones, 33.
  - Images of Columns with Angels Blowing Trumpets, 34.
  - Sections Involving "A Distinguished Collection of Songs" for Senior Choir, Gospel Chorus, and Soloist, 35.
  - Illustrations, 36.
  - Jesus Image, 37.
  - Images of Letters and Numbers, 38.
  - Sections for "Music For The Home and The Church", 39.
  - "Pace's Praises, No. 1," Title Bar, 40.
  - "Pace's Praises," title bars, 41.
  - Promotional Jingle, 42.
  - Rose Image, 43.
  - Tempo Markings, 44.
  - Images for "WORDS & MUSIC by CHAS. H. PACE", 45.
  - Front Page of "Catalog of Pace Songs", 46.
  - Invoices, 47.
  - Membership Roster, 49.
  - Price Lists for Various Pace Songs, 50.
  - Two Sections of "Send for our Catalog of Songs", 51.
  - Shipping Order Form, 52.
  - Blank Negatives, 53.
  - Page-Proofs of Advertisements of Various Music Publications, 54.
  - Printed Image of Angel Blowing Trumpet on Column, 55.
  - Printed Image of Cross, 56.
  - Page proofs for numbers, 57.
  - Page-Proofs for "Pace's Senior Choir and Advanced Gospel Chorus Edition", 58.
  - Various Page-Proofs for "Published By Chas. H. Pace", 59.
  - Page-Proofs of "Send for our Catalog of Songs by Chas. H. Pace", 60.
  - Page-Proofs Designating Solo or Chorus Songs, 61.
  - Page-Proofs of Song and Price Lists, 62.
  - Tempo Page-Proofs, 63.
  - Page-Proofs of The Old Ship of Zion's Address, 64.
  - Various Page-Proofs of Title Bars, 65.
  - Miscellaneous Page-Proofs, 66.
- Printed Music, 1933-1951; III.
  - "Hide My Soul," 25 Copies, 1943; 1.
  - "Hide My Soul," 25 Copies, 1943; 2.
  - "Hide My Soul," 25 Copies, 1943; 3.
  - "Hide My Soul," 25 Copies, 1943; 4.
  - "Hide My Soul," 25 Copies, 1943; 5.
  - "Hide My Soul," 25 Copies, 1943; 6.
  - "I'm Not Ashamed To Say I Love Him", 28 Copies, 7.
  - "I'm Not Ashamed To Say I Love Him," 25 Copies, 8.
  - "I'm Not Ashamed To Say I Love Him," 1 Copy of Page 3, 9.
  - "I'm Not Ashamed To Say I Love Him," 1 Copy of Page 4, 10.
  - "I'm Not Ashamed To Say I Love Him," 98 Copies of Pages 3-4, 11.
  - "I'm Not Ashamed To Say I Love Him," 98 Copies of Pages 3-4, 12.
  - "I Shouted Joy," 1 Copy of Pages 3-4, 13.
  - "Jericho," 50 Copies of Pages 3-6, 14.
  - "Jericho," 50 Copies of Pages 3-6, 15.
  - "Jericho," 50 Copies of Pages 3-6, 16.
  - "Jericho," 50 Copies of Pages 3-6, 17.